pensketruckrental.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Penske Truck Rental

## Are You Concerned About Your Privacy?

### We respect your privacy by implementing tough information security.

It is our responsibility to treat customers, colleagues, the community, and the environment with respect. That includes your personal information. We ensure your privacy by handling your personal information in a safe and accountable manner.

### Penske Truck Rental Privacy Policy for Internet Websites

**Contents**

  * Collection of personal information
  * Collection of aggregate information
  * Cookies and tracking technology
  * Advertising/online tracking
  * Security
  * Right to monitor use
  * How Penske discloses personal information
  * How Penske protects personal information
  * Links to third-party sites
  * California privacy rights
  * Children’s privacy
  * Your consent
  * Reviewing and modifying your personal information
  * Opting out
  * Changes to policy

Penske Truck Leasing Co., L.P. and its subsidiaries ("Penske") understand our customers' concern about privacy and the use of their personal information. Use of any information gathered from or about our customers through the Penske internet websites (the "Sites") shall be governed by the Sites' Terms of Use (www.pensketruckrental.com/terms-and-conditions/) and this Privacy Policy. Penske encourages you to read this Privacy Policy in full to learn how Penske treats personal information obtained while visiting our Sites, and we encourage you to check back regularly for any updates. Use of the Sites indicates your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, the Sites' Terms of Use, and Penske's use of your information as described below.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, or our Sites, please contact a Penske representative at 1-888-234-4201 or via email at [privacy@penske.com](mailto:privacy@penske.com), or via mail to Chief Compliance Officer, Penske Truck Leasing Co., L.P., 2675 Morgantown Road, Reading, PA 19607. 

### Collection of personal information

We collect personal information in various ways to better serve you. Such information may be used to allow you to order or schedule services, to receive support for the services we provide, to allow us to contact you to provide those services, to complete delivery of products and services, and to protect Penske from fraudulent transactions. We also use the information we collect to tailor and improve your experience while using the Sites.

Once you access the Sites and/or transact business with Penske, we may collect personally identifiable information about you. Such personally identifiable information may include e-mail addresses, domain names, addresses and routing information; your name and phone number; your mailing and/or billing addresses; and other relevant data that will better allow us to provide information and/or services related to your needs. We may also receive information from consumer credit reporting agencies, credit references, employers and insurance agencies such as your credit history, credit worthiness, and information obtained to verify employment history or current insurance coverage. We collect information from cookies (see below) and other technology to track your website usage with us and to provide you with customized content, among other things. Penske will not rent or sell your name, address, credit card information, or other personal information to any third party.

### Collection of aggregate information

In addition to the personally identifiable information described above, we also collect aggregate information from many users about use of the Sites, such as number of visits and pages visited, and the overall duration of time spent on the Sites. The information we collect depends in large part upon the needs of your account and what services and features you use on the Sites. We do not disclose this information to third parties.

### Cookie and tracking technology

When you enter information or otherwise navigate through the Sites, the Sites use temporary "cookies" or other tracking methods to recognize you and your access privileges on the Sites, to facilitate the interaction between you and the Sites, and to track Site usage. A "cookie" is a small string of text that a website can send to your browser for storage by your hard drive that allows us to provide you with tailored information and services by recognizing your hard drive when you return to the Sites. If you choose to do so, you may opt out of the use of cookies through your browser's options. If you refuse cookies, you may find that some services do not function properly or may be considerably slower.

### Advertising/online tracking

Penske uses online advertising programs (including but not limited to Google Adwords Remarketing) to serve ads on third-party websites. These programs use cookies and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads for their clients, and to display relevant ads tailored to you based on your visit to our Sites.

You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from many websites by using the opt-out tools available through the Digital Advertising Alliance ([www.digitaladvertisingalliance.org](http://www.digitaladvertisingalliance.org/)) or the Network Advertising Initiative ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). You can opt out of Google AdWords Remarketing by visiting Google's Ads Preferences Manager (<https://www.google.com/settings/ads>).

### Security

The security of customer information is very important to us, and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard non-public personal information about you.

When our credit pre-approval form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as social security numbers), that information is encrypted and is protected with 128-bit or greater SSL encryption software, an industry standard for reputable organizations. While on a secure page, such as our credit pre-approval application form, the website address will begin with https://...

Furthermore, once the information has been received by us, we use security procedures and policies commensurate with industry standards to safeguard against loss, theft, unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and/or disclosure.

### Right to monitor use

Penske reserves the right, without any obligation, to monitor your use of the Sites for the purpose of ensuring compliance with the Sites' Terms of Use (www.pensketruckrental.com/terms-and-conditions/). Penske further reserves the right to prohibit conduct, communications, or content that it deems in its discretion to be harmful, abusive, offensive or hateful to Penske, its affiliates, or to any of Penske's customers and/or users of the Sites, or that may otherwise violate the law.

### How Penske discloses personal information

Penske may, from time to time, share your personal information for the following purposes:

  * **Agents and Affiliates:** Penske may distribute the personally identifiable information that you submit to us, both internally within our company and to our agents and affiliates as necessary for purposes related to our products and services. We may also use this information to help us manage programs and services that may be of interest to you.
  * **Service Providers/Marketing Partners:** We provide information to third parties to assist us in providing service to our customers, responding to customer inquiries, and servicing, administering, and enforcing our accounts. We may also use marketing and other firms to assist us in our own marketing efforts. These third-party service providers may use customer information to perform contracted services at our request. 
  * **Co-Brand Products or Services:** Certain products or services are provided in partnership with identified co-brand partner(s), and when you access Penske products and/or services through co-brand partner(s), you agree that Penske may share personal information (excluding credit card numbers) with such co-brand partner(s). If you elect to purchase or register for products and/or services offered through co-brand partner(s), your personal information will be transferred to such co-brand partner(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such co-brand partner(s). Penske does not control such privacy policies and encourages you to review the privacy policies of such co-brand partner(s) closely.
  * **Marketing Partners for Certain Products or Services:** Penske may share personal information (excluding credit card numbers) with the marketing partner(s) identified in checkout/reservation, but only where you agree during checkout/reservation that you would like your information shared for their marketing purposes. If you elect to have your information shared with such marketing partner(s), your personal information will be transferred to such marketing partner(s) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such marketing partner(s). Penske does not control such privacy policies and encourages you to review the privacy policies of such marketing partner(s) closely.
  * **Administrative or Legal Process:** At times Penske may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. Penske may disclose information about you, in our sole discretion, if Penske believes that disclosure is necessary (a) to satisfy any law, regulation, governmental request or to respond to a subpoena; (b) to operate this website; (c) to protect the safety, rights or property of Penske or users of this Site or any of Penske's websites; or (d) as otherwise permitted under this Privacy Policy.
  * **Business Transfers:** In the event that Penske sells or transfers all or a portion of our business and assets, we reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information in connection with that transaction. In such event, Penske will use reasonable efforts to ensure that your personally identifiable information remains protected.

### How we protect personal information

Penske takes appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial precautions in our efforts to prevent unauthorized access to and use of any data you send us. We recommend that when you access the Site, you do so from a secure browser. We also recommend that when passwords are requested or required to access the Sites, you select a unique combination of letters and numbers in order to protect your information.

### Links to third-party sites

The Sites may contain links to other third-party sites, such as the sites of Penske agents, sales affiliates, and other organizations whose products or services may be of interest to you. We cannot be responsible for maintaining your privacy once you leave our Sites. When you click on any links or banners on our Site that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies and practices. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of any and every site you visit, whether you are linking from one of our Sites or browsing on your own.

### California privacy rights

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, a California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship has the right to request certain information regarding the disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@penske.com](mailto:privacy@penske.com) with the subject line "California Privacy Rights," or write to Penske at:

Chief Compliance Officer—California Privacy Rights

Penske Truck Leasing Co., L.P  
2675 Morgantown Road  
Reading, PA 19607

### Children's privacy

Penske does not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from children under the age of sixteen (16) or allow such children to participate in any services offered on the Sites that require the submission of user information. Should Penske learn that someone under the age of sixteen (16) has provided any personal information to or on any of the Sites, Penske will take steps to remove that information as soon as possible.

### Your consent

As a condition to using the Sites, we require your approval to collect the personally identifiable information discussed above. By visiting the Sites, you agree that we may collect and use this information, as stated in our policy. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so you are always informed about what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Thank you for taking the time to review our Privacy Policy. Should you have questions or require additional information, please contact us via the email address or telephone number in the first paragraph above.

### Reviewing and modifying your personal information

If you wish at any time to verify or modify any of the information you have submitted to us, please contact a Penske representative at 1-888-234-4201 or via email at [privacy@penske.com](mailto:privacy@penske.com).

### Opting out

Penske gives you the opportunity to opt out of receiving direct marketing information from us. You can easily opt out by sending an email to [privacy@penske.com](mailto:privacy@penske.com), or by calling us at 1-888-234-4201.

### Changes to policy

Penske has the right, at its sole discretion, to modify this policy at any time, and such changes will take effect when they are posted here. You agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time and any updates that we provide regarding changes to this policy.

This Privacy Policy was last updated March 2016.  
Copyright © 2011, 2015 Penske Truck Leasing Co., L.P. All Rights reserved.
